okay this is uh Aaron and Sammy session
six operation get strong and
sexy here is Aaron on back squats today
this is 95 lbs um so Aaron did her
workout first and then Sammy followed
that's 115 so I'm just having to do
singles this is
125 and look at this these are she is
smoking these weights this is
135 uh she gets below parallel and Nails
it so that's 135 lbs that is her when
she first started her Max was like 95 is
or so so she's put on like 40 lbs on her
squat in the last month month and a half
or so two months um so that's a PR
that's a huge PR for Aaron I could not I
was so happy she got that I can't even
begin to tell you how excited I was and
now we wanted to do a rep record for uh
dead lless um I don't even know how many
she got here I think she got six or
something or I don't know and then
uh well here she is
um with this is um
145 uh that first rep I don't know if
you saw she jerked the weight up that's
common so that's what I told her for the
next set don't jerk this is great form
keeps the bar close to her very happy
with her form here here's her next set
so here she doesn't jerk the weight up
it's nice and smooth and this this is
just flying up she did um three sets of
five with
135 week
one and then
uh week two she did 140 and now this is
week three she did 145 so she's moving
up 5 lbs each week which won't keep
happening indefinitely but
um anyway this she was sore because this
this uh this was done on Thursday their
last workout was on Tuesday days so
they're still sore usually we do their
two workouts more spaced out
more okay and then uh that was a a one
rep max I think that was
165 for
um 165lb deadlift that's her Max
conventionally she's done 185 I believe
Sumo but Aaron's stronger Sumo and then
this is bench press this is 85 lb then
we have 95
lb so today got a a one rep max on bench
squats and deadlifts that's a 95 lb so
that's a PR and then I had her rep out
with uh
65 so that that 95 lb she just got was
also a PR um so awesome day for Aaron
she was fatigued she was still sore a
little bit beat up from the workout two
days prior and squatted 135 deadlifted
uh 165 after already doing sets of
deadlifts and then bench 95 so these are
all
PRS and uh and I was very happy with the
form too so keeping good form and
setting PRS uh what more can you ask
for okay next up uh I had Aon do one set
of goblet squats this is 60 lbs this is
very heavy for her to
hold
um this a good exercise for Aaron
because it's really hard for her to hold
for the upper back when it's this heavy
she only weighs 100 so that's 60% of her
body weight and um she has to get her
elbows in between her knees there so it
makes her push the knees out and then
this here is uh barbell glute Bridges uh
this is um that barbell weighs 70 lb so
this is a 120 this 120 lb she gets 20
reps again she was beat up from uh two
sessions ago so I didn't want her to do
too much of volume this is a good
exercise for and that that thick bar
there that axle bar makes it real easy
to uh it's comfortable on the hips and
then we duct taped that yoga mat over it
so it's very
comfortable um and then I tried to have
Aaron do um glute ham raises she gets a
lot of anterior pelvic tilt and Lumbar
extension there so I didn't really but
she can do these that's the first time
with her ever doing these I didn't like
those I wanted to do a little extra
hamstring work so then I switched I
didn't like the good the glute ham
raises so I switched to good mornings
and this is 65 lb she gets 10 reps easy
she has very good form with good
mornings um this looked
great and
uh good exercise for look how she sits
back gets soft knees the knees aren't
straight but sits way back it's a big
stretch in the
hammies
um in the you'd like to have tons of
specificity and also tens tons of
assistance work but you got to kind of
pick your
battles here's
a inverted Rose now I'm just having to
do one set of the different assistance
lifts just because she's beat up I
wanted and set PRS today so I wanted her
to get some good resting
in
um think she gets 10 or
um and now here's
Sammy uh Sammy was really sore this is
135 lb squat she gets three
reps now this is
185 uh she was feeling
sore
so skimps on that one didn't quite reach
depth three reps there and then this is
205 uh so we just went for a single so
that's a PR for Sammy a
205b squat might not have quite gotten
parallel but she's really sore today now
I wanted to do pause squats and hold it
there for three for a count of
three uh so here she is doing pause
squats gets uh three reps with 135 now
here's deadlifts conventional deadlifts
this is
135 looks easy but uh again she's she's
sore from two two nights ago they had to
work out on Tuesday and Thursday this
week um so she's still sore so just
warming her up and jump jump to
225 and
uh she's looking side to side I don't
like that here she sets up in valgus a
little bit wider stance I don't like
that she she I wasn't paying attention
but this is
245 uh or 2 sorry I think that was 250
which that's a PR for her so a 255 lb PR
so she's she still PR on the squat and
on the deadlift even though the form was
not that good and she's fatigued so
she'll do better next week that's an 85
lb bench press now here's 95 lbs I was
very happy with a form here good
pause little bit wobbly but sets a PR on
the bench too now this is a barbell
glute bridge this is a remember that
bars 70 lb it's an axle bar so this is
170 170 I think she gets like 20 reps
here
uh Sammy has not done a lot of barbell
glute bridging she's always just done
hip thrust um she likes hip thrust more
but it's good to do both it's good to do
barbell glute Bridges and hip thrust um
and Samy sore I'm not trying to work her
too hard what nice as they get Thursday
uh sorry Friday Saturday Sunday and
Monday off so on Tuesday they'll be
really strong and next
week um and then some band seated hip
abductions and uh I think that's it
for uh session six so very happy with
the girls progress this week They al
they both set PRS they're both on track
form looked good and uh next week we'll
keep it up and keep going for more PRS
so that's it for uh session session six
uh I hope you've enjoyed the videos um
thank you very much for watching good